include "Metadata/StatDescriptions/stat_descriptions.txt"
description
	1 village_can_disenchant_up_to_rarity
	3
		1 "Can Disenchant Magic Equipment Items"
		2 "Can Disenchant Magic or Rare Equipment Items"
		3 "Can Disenchant Magic, Rare or Unique Equipment Items"
	lang "Russian"
	3
		1 "Может распылять волшебное снаряжение"
		2 "Может распылять волшебное и редкое снаряжение"
		3 "Может распылять волшебное, редкое и уникальное снаряжение"
	lang "German"
	3
		1 "Kann magische Ausrüstungsgegenstände entzaubern"
		2 "Kann magische oder seltene Ausrüstungsgegenstände entzaubern"
		3 "Kann magische, seltene oder einzigartige Ausrüstungsgegenstände entzaubern"
	lang "Spanish"
	3
		1 "Puedes desencantar objetos de equipamiento mágicos"
		2 "Puedes desencantar objetos de equipamiento mágicos o raros"
		3 "Puedes desencantar objetos de equipamiento mágicos, raros o únicos"
	lang "Thai"
	3
		1 "สลาย ไอเทมสวมใส่เมจิก ได้"
		2 "สลาย ไอเทมสวมใส่เมจิกหรือแรร์ ได้"
		3 "สลาย ไอเทมสวมใส่เมจิก, แรร์ หรือ ยูนิค ได้"
	lang "Korean"
	3
		1 "마법 장비 아이템 인챈트 해제 가능"
		2 "마법, 희귀 장비 아이템 인챈트 해제 가능"
		3 "마법, 희귀, 고유 장비 아이템 인챈트 해제 가능"
	lang "Japanese"
	3
		1 "マジックの装備アイテムのエンチャントを解呪できる"
		2 "マジックまたはレアの装備アイテムのエンチャントを解呪できる"
		3 "マジック、レアまたはユニークの装備アイテムのエンチャントを解呪できる"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	3
		1 "可破幻魔法裝備物品"
		2 "可破幻魔法或稀有裝備物品"
		3 "可破幻魔法、稀有或傳奇裝備物品"
	lang "Portuguese"
	3
		1 "Pode Desencantar Equipamentos Mágicos"
		2 "Pode Desencantar Equipamentos Mágicos ou Raros"
		3 "Pode Desencantar Equipamentos Mágicos, Raros ou Únicos"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	3	
		1 "可以分解魔法装备物品"
		2 "可以分解魔法或稀有装备物品"
		3 "可以分解魔法，稀有或传奇装备物品"
	lang "French"
	3
		1 "Peut Désenchanter les Équipements Magiques"
		2 "Peut Désenchanter les Équipements Magiques et Rares"
		3 "Peut Désenchanter les Équipements Magiques, Rares et Uniques"

description
	1 village_can_farm_crops_up_to_rank
	5
		1 "Farming Plots can grow Wheat"
		2 "Farming Plots can grow Wheat and Corn"
		3 "Farming Plots can grow Wheat, Corn and Pumpkin"
		4 "Farming Plots can grow Wheat, Corn, Pumpkin and Orgourd"
		5|# "Farming Plots can grow Wheat, Corn, Pumpkin, Orgourd and Blue Zanthimum"
	lang "Russian"
	5
		1 "Фермерские участки могут выращивать пшеницу"
		2 "Фермерские участки могут выращивать пшеницу и кукурузу"
		3 "Фермерские участки могут выращивать пшеницу, кукурузу и тыкву"
		4 "Фермерские участки могут выращивать пшеницу, кукурузу, тыкву и огурцы"
		5|# "Фермерские участки могут выращивать пшеницу, кукурузу, тыкву, огурцы и синий зантимий"
	lang "German"
	5
		1 "An Anbauflächen kann Weizen angebaut werden"
		2 "An Anbauflächen können Weizen und Mais angebaut werden"
		3 "An Anbauflächen können Weizen, Mais und Kürbisse angebaut werden"
		4 "An Anbauflächen können Weizen, Mais, Kürbisse und Orgourd angebaut werden"
		5|# "An Anbauflächen können Weizen, Mais, Kürbisse, Orgourd und Blaues Zanthimum angebaut werden"
	lang "Spanish"
	5
		1 "En las parcelas de cultivo puedes plantar trigo"
		2 "En las parcelas de cultivo puedes plantar trigo y maíz"
		3 "En las parcelas de cultivo puedes plantar trigo, maíz y calabazas"
		4 "En las parcelas de cultivo puedes plantar trigo, maíz, calabazas y calabazul"
		5|# "En las parcelas de cultivo puedes plantar trigo, maíz, calabazas, calabazul y zantimum azul"
	lang "Thai"
	5
		1 "แปลงเพาะปลูกปลูก ข้าวสาลี ได้"
		2 "แปลงเพาะปลูกปลูก ข้าวสาลีและข้าวโพด ได้"
		3 "แปลงเพาะปลูกปลูก ข้าวสาลี, ข้าวโพด, ฟักทอง ได้"
		4 "แปลงเพาะปลูกปลูก ข้าวสาลี, ข้าวโพด, ฟักทอง, ออร์กอร์ด ได้"
		5|# "แปลงเพาะปลูกปลูก ข้าวสาลี, ข้าวโพด, ฟักทอง, ออร์กอร์ด, แซนธิมัมฟ้า ได้"
	lang "Korean"
	5
		1 "경작지에서 밀 재배 가능"
		2 "경작지에서 밀, 옥수수 재배 가능"
		3 "경작지에서 밀, 옥수수, 호박 재배 가능"
		4 "경작지에서 밀, 옥수수, 호박, 오르박 재배 가능"
		5|# "경작지에서 밀, 옥수수, 호박, 오르박, 푸른도꼬마리 재배 가능"
	lang "Japanese"
	5
		1 "農地では小麦を栽培できる"
		2 "農地では小麦およびトウモロコシを栽培できる"
		3 "農地では小麦、トウモロコシおよびカボチャを栽培できる"
		4 "農地では小麦、トウモロコシ、カボチャおよびウミヒョウタンを栽培できる"
		5|# "農地では小麦、トウモロコシ、カボチャ、ウミヒョウタンおよびザンシマムを栽培できる"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	5
		1 "農地可種植小麥"
		2 "農地可種植小麥和玉米"
		3 "農地可種植小麥、玉米和南瓜"
		4 "農地可種植小麥、玉米、南瓜和瓜果"
		5|# "農地可種植小麥、玉米、南瓜、瓜果和藍贊提蒙"
	lang "Portuguese"
	5
		1 "Plantações podem gerar Trigo"
		2 "Plantações podem gerar Trigo e Milho"
		3 "Plantações podem gerar Trigo, Milho e Abóboras"
		4 "Plantações podem gerar Trigo, Milho, Abóboras e Cabaças"
		5|# "Plantações podem gerar Trigo, Milho, Abóboras, Cabaças e Zântimo Azul"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	5	
		1 "耕作田现在可以种植小麦"
		2 "耕作田现在可以种植小麦和玉米"
		3 "耕作田现在可以种植小麦，玉米和南瓜"
		4 "耕作田现在可以种植小麦，玉米，南瓜和金葫芦"
		5|# "耕作田现在可以种植小麦，玉米，南瓜，金葫芦和蓝翠花"
	lang "French"
	5
		1 "Les Plantations peuvent faire pousser du Blé"
		2 "Les Plantations peuvent faire pousser du Blé et du Maïs"
		3 "Les Plantations peuvent faire pousser du Blé, du Maïs et des Citrouilles"
		4 "Les Plantations peuvent faire pousser du Blé, du Maïs, des Citrouilles et de l'Orgourd"
		5|# "Les Plantations peuvent faire pousser du Blé, du Maïs, des Citrouilles, de l'Orgourd et du Zanthium bleu"

description
	1 village_can_mega_reroll
	1
		# "Raulf offers an Improved Reroll"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "라울프가 향상된 무작위 변경 제공"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "Raul bietet eine verbesserte Auswahl an"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Raulf oferece uma Rolagem Melhorada"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "Ральф позволяет пользоваться улучшенным обновлением списка для найма"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "ราล์ฟเสนอ การสุ่มดีเด่น"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "ラウルフが提供するリロールの質が良くなる"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Raulf ofrece una aleatorización mejorada"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "勞爾夫提供優化的重骰"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "Raulf offre un Nouveau tirage Amélioré"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "劳尔夫提供一次强化重置"

description
	1 village_can_mine_ores_up_to_rank
	5
		1 "Can Mine Crimson Iron"
		2 "Can Mine Crimson Iron and Orichalcum"
		3 "Can Mine Crimson Iron, Orichalcum and Petrified Amber"
		4 "Can Mine Crimson Iron, Orichalcum, Petrified Amber and Bismuth"
		5|# "Can Mine Crimson Iron, Orichalcum, Petrified Amber, Bismuth and Verisium"
	lang "Russian"
	5
		1 "Может добывать багровое железо"
		2 "Может добывать багровое железо и орихалк"
		3 "Может добывать багровое железо, орихалк и окаменелый янтарь"
		4 "Может добывать багровое железо, орихалк, окаменелый янтарь и висмут"
		5|# "Может добывать багровое железо, орихалк, окаменелый янтарь, висмут и веризий"
	lang "German"
	5
		1 "Kann Blutrotes Eisen abbauen"
		2 "Kann Blutrotes Eisen und Oreichalkos abbauen"
		3 "Kann Blutrotes Eisen, Oreichalkos und Amberium abbauen"
		4 "Kann Blutrotes Eisen, Oreichalkos, Amberium und Bismut abbauen"
		5|# "Kann Blutrotes Eisen, Oreichalkos, Amberium, Bismut und Verisium abbauen"
	lang "Spanish"
	5
		1 "Puedes extraer hierro carmesí"
		2 "Puedes extraer hierro carmesí y oricalco"
		3 "Puedes extraer hierro carmesí, oricalco y ámbar petrificado"
		4 "Puedes extraer hierro carmesí, oricalco, ámbar petrificado y bismuto"
		5|# "Puedes extraer hierro carmesí, oricalco, ámbar petrificado, bismuto y verisium"
	lang "Thai"
	5
		1 "ขุด เหล็กเลือดนก ได้"
		2 "ขุด เหล็กเลือดนกและโอริคัลคุม ได้"
		3 "ขุด เหล็กเลือดนก, โอริคัลคุม, หินอำพัน ได้"
		4 "ขุด เหล็กเลือดนก, โอริคัลคุม, หินอำพัน, บิสมัท ได้"
		5|# "ขุด เหล็กเลือดนก, โอริคัลคุม, หินอำพัน, บิสมัท, เวรีเซียม ได้"
	lang "Korean"
	5
		1 "진홍철 채광 가능"
		2 "진홍철, 오리칼쿰 채광 가능"
		3 "진홍철, 오리칼쿰, 석화 호박 채광 가능"
		4 "진홍철, 오리칼쿰, 석화 호박, 비스무트 채광 가능"
		5|# "진홍철, 오리칼쿰, 석화 호박, 비스무트, 베리시움 채광 가능"
	lang "Japanese"
	5
		1 "クリムゾンアイアンを採掘できる"
		2 "クリムゾンアイアンおよびオリハルコンを採掘できる"
		3 "クリムゾンアイアン、オリハルコンおよび石化琥珀を採掘できる"
		4 "クリムゾンアイアン、オリハルコン、石化琥珀およびビスマスを採掘できる"
		5|# "クリムゾンアイアン、オリハルコン、石化琥珀、ビスマスおよびヴェリシウムを採掘できる"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	5
		1 "可開採緋紅鍛鐵"
		2 "可開採緋紅鍛鐵和山銅"
		3 "可開採緋紅鍛鐵、山銅和石化琥珀"
		4 "可開採緋紅鍛鐵、山銅、石化琥珀和鉍"
		5|# "可開採緋紅鍛鐵、山銅、石化琥珀、鉍和維里西姆"
	lang "Portuguese"
	5
		1 "Pode Minerar Ferro Carmesim"
		2 "Pode Minerar Ferro Carmesim e Oricálco"
		3 "Pode Minerar Ferro Carmesim, Oricálco e Âmbar Petrificado"
		4 "Pode Minerar Ferro Carmesim, Oricálco, Âmbar Petrificado e Bismuto"
		5|# "Pode Minerar Ferro Carmesim, Oricálco, Âmbar Petrificado, Bismuto e Verísio"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	5
		1 "可以采掘绯红铁矿石"
		2 "可以采掘绯红铁矿石和奥利哈刚矿石"
		3 "可以采掘绯红铁矿石，奥利哈刚矿石和石化琥珀矿石"
		4 "可以采掘绯红铁矿石，奥利哈刚矿石，石化琥珀矿石和铋矿石"
		5|# "可以采掘绯红铁矿石，奥利哈刚矿石，石化琥珀矿石，铋矿石和维金矿石"
	lang "French"
	5
		1 "Peut miner du Fer écarlate"
		2 "Peut miner du Fer écarlate et de l'Orichalque"
		3 "Peut miner du Fer écarlate, de l'Orichalque et de l'Ambre pétrifié"
		4 "Peut miner du Fer écarlate, de l'Orichalque, de l'Ambre pétrifié et du Bismuth"
		5|# "Peut miner du Fer écarlate, de l'Orichalque, de l'Ambre pétrifié, du Bismuth et du Vérisium"

description
	1 village_can_recombinate_up_to_X
	3
		1 "Can Recombinate Weapons"
		2 "Can Recombinate Weapons and Armour"
		3|# "Can Recombinate Weapons, Armour, Jewellery and Idols"
	lang "Spanish"
	3
		1 "Puedes recombinar armas"
		2 "Puedes recombinar armas y armaduras"
		3|# "Puedes recombinar armas, armaduras, joyería e ídolos"
	lang "Japanese"
	3
		1 "武器をリコンビネートできる"
		2 "武器と防具をリコンビネートできる"
		3|# "武器、防具、宝飾品およびアイドルをリコンビネートできる"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	3
		1 "可以重组武器"
		2 "可以重组武器和护甲"
		3|# "可以重组武器，护甲、饰品和雕像"
	lang "French"
	3
		1 "Peut Recombiner les Armes"
		2 "Peut Recombiner les Armes et Armures"
		3|# "Peut Recombiner les Armes, Armures, Accessoires et Idoles"
	lang "German"
	3
		1 "Kann Waffen rekombinieren"
		2 "Kann Waffen und Rüstung rekombinieren"
		3|# "Kann Waffen, Rüstung, Schmuck und Götzen rekombinieren"
	lang "Portuguese"
	3
		1 "Pode Recombinar Armas"
		2 "Pode Recombinar Armas e Armaduras"
		3|# "Pode Recombinar Armas, Armaduras, Acessórios e Ídolos"
	lang "Russian"
	3
		1 "Может рекомбинировать оружие"
		2 "Может рекомбинировать оружие и броню"
		3|# "Может рекомбинировать оружие, броню, бижутерию и идолы"
	lang "Thai"
	3
		1 "ผสม อาวุธ ได้"
		2 "ผสม อาวุธและเกราะ ได้"
		3|# "ผสม อาวุธ, เกราะ, เครื่องประดับ, เทวรูป ได้"
	lang "Korean"
	3
		1 "무기 재조합 가능"
		2 "무기, 방어구 재조합 가능"
		3|# "무기, 방어구, 장신구, 우상 재조합 가능"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	3
		1 "可以重新組合武器"
		2 "可以重新組合武器和護甲"
		3|# "可以重新組合武器、護甲、飾品和魔偶"

description
	1 village_can_run_maps_up_to_tier
	4
		1|5 "Atlas Runners can run White Maps"
		6|10 "Atlas Runners can run White and Yellow Maps"
		11|16 "Atlas Runners can run White, Yellow and Red Maps"
		17|# "Atlas Runners can run White, Yellow, Red and Purple Maps"
	lang "Portuguese"
	4
		1|5 "Mapeadores do Atlas podem fazer Mapas Brancos"
		6|10 "Mapeadores do Atlas podem fazer Mapas Brancos e Amarelos"
		11|16 "Mapeadores do Atlas podem fazer Mapas Brancos, Amarelos e Vermelhos"
		17|# "Mapeadores do Atlas podem fazer Mapas Brancos, Amarelos, Vermelhos e Roxos"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	4
		1|5 "輿圖探索者可以刷白色地圖"
		6|10 "輿圖探索者可以刷白色和黃色地圖"
		11|16 "輿圖探索者可以刷白色、黃色和紅色地圖"
		17|# "輿圖探索者可以刷白色、黃色、紅色和紫色地圖"
	lang "Korean"
	4
		1|5 "아틀라스 탐험가가 하얀 지도 공략 가능"
		6|10 "아틀라스 탐험가가 하얀 지도 및 노란 지도 공략 가능"
		11|16 "아틀라스 탐험가가 하얀 지도, 노란 지도, 빨간 지도 공략 가능"
		17|# "아틀라스 탐험가가 하얀 지도, 노란 지도, 빨간 지도, 보라색 지도 공략 가능"
	lang "German"
	4
		1|5 "Atlasläufer können weiße Karten laufen"
		6|10 "Atlasläufer können weiße und gelbe Karten laufen"
		11|16 "Atlasläufer können weiße, gelbe und rote Karten laufen"
		17|# "Atlasläufer können weiße, gelbe, rote und violette Karten laufen"
	lang "Russian"
	4
		1|5 "Исследователи Атласа могут проходить белые карты"
		6|10 "Исследователи Атласа могут проходить белые и желтые карты"
		11|16 "Исследователи Атласа могут проходить белые, желтые и красные карты"
		17|# "Исследователи Атласа могут проходить белые, желтые, красные и фиолетовые карты"
	lang "Thai"
	4
		1|5 "นักผจญแผนที่ บุก แผนที่ขาว ได้"
		6|10 "นักผจญแผนที่ บุก แผนที่ขาวและเหลือง ได้"
		11|16 "นักผจญแผนที่ บุก แผนที่ขาว, เหลือง, แดง ได้"
		17|# "นักผจญแผนที่ บุก แผนที่ขาว, เหลือง, แดง, ม่วง ได้"
	lang "Japanese"
	4
		1|5 "アトラスランナーは白マップを走れる"
		6|10 "アトラスランナーは白マップおよび黄マップを走れる"
		11|16 "アトラスランナーは白マップ、黄マップおよび赤マップを走れる"
		17|# "アトラスランナーは白マップ、黄マップ、赤マップおよび紫マップを走れる"
	lang "Spanish"
	4
		1|5 "Los exploradores del Atlas pueden explorar mapas blancos"
		6|10 "Los exploradores del Atlas pueden explorar mapas blancos y amarillos"
		11|16 "Los exploradores del Atlas pueden explorar mapas blancos, amarillos y rojos"
		17|# "Los exploradores del Atlas pueden explorar mapas blancos, amarillos, rojos y morados"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	4	
		1|5 "异界冒险者可以挑战白色地图"
		6|10 "异界冒险者可以挑战白色和黄色地图"
		11|16 "异界冒险者可以挑战白色，黄色和红色地图"
		17|# "异界冒险者可以挑战白色，黄色，红色和紫色地图"
	lang "French"
	4
		1|5 "Les Explorateurs de l'Atlas peuvent faire des Cartes Blanches"
		6|10 "Les Explorateurs de l'Atlas peuvent faire des Cartes Blanches et Jaunes"
		11|16 "Les Explorateurs de l'Atlas peuvent faire des Cartes Blanches, Jaunes et Rouges"
		17|# "Les Explorateurs de l'Atlas peuvent faire des Cartes Blanches, Jaunes, Rouges et Violettes"

description
	1 village_can_ship_to_x_ports
	5
		1 "Can Ship to Riben Fell"
		2 "Can Ship to Riben Fell and Ngakanu"
		3 "Can Ship to Riben Fell, Ngakanu and Pondium"
		4 "Can Ship to Riben Fell, Ngakanu, Pondium and Te Onui"
		5|# "Can Ship to Riben Fell, Ngakanu, Pondium, Te Onui and Kalguur"
	lang "Portuguese"
	5
		1 "Pode Exportar para Riben Fell"
		2 "Pode Exportar para Riben Fell e Ngakanu"
		3 "Pode Exportar para Riben Fell, Ngakanu e Pondium"
		4 "Pode Exportar para Riben Fell, Ngakanu, Pondium e Te Onui"
		5|# "Pode Exportar para Riben Fell, Ngakanu, Pondium, Te Onui e Kalguur"
	lang "Thai"
	5
		1 "ขนส่งไปยัง ริเบน เฟล ได้"
		2 "ขนส่งไปยัง ริเบน เฟลและนาคานู ได้"
		3 "ขนส่งไปยัง ริเบน เฟล, นาคานู, พอนเดียม ได้"
		4 "ขนส่งไปยัง ริเบน เฟล, นาคานู, พอนเดียม, เท โอนุย ได้"
		5|# "ขนส่งไปยัง ริเบน เฟล, นาคานู, พอนเดียม, เท โอนุย และ คาลเกอร์ ได้"
	lang "German"
	5
		1 "Kann verschiffen nach Ribeby"
		2 "Kann verschiffen nach Ribeby und Ngakanu"
		3 "Kann verschiffen nach Ribeby, Ngakanu und Pondium"
		4 "Kann verschiffen nach Ribeby, Ngakanu, Pondium und Te Onui"
		5|# "Kann verschiffen nach Ribeby, Ngakanu, Pondium, Te Onui und Kalguur"
	lang "Russian"
	5
		1 "Может отправлять корабли в Рибенфелл"
		2 "Может отправлять корабли в Рибенфелл и Нгакану"
		3 "Может отправлять корабли в Рибенфелл, Нгакану и Пондий"
		4 "Может отправлять корабли в Рибенфелл, Нгакану, Пондий и Те Онуи"
		5|# "Может отправлять корабли в Рибенфелл, Нгакану, Пондий, Те Онуи и Калгууран"
	lang "Spanish"
	5
		1 "Puedes comerciar con Ribera clara"
		2 "Puedes comerciar con Ribera clara y Ngakanu"
		3 "Puedes comerciar con Ribera clara, Ngakanu y Pondium"
		4 "Puedes comerciar con Ribera clara, Ngakanu, Pondium y Te Onui"
		5|# "Puedes comerciar con Ribera clara, Ngakanu, Pondium, Te Onui y Kalguur"
	lang "Korean"
	5
		1 "리벤펠로 운송 가능"
		2 "리벤펠 및 응가카누로 운송 가능"
		3 "리벤펠, 응가카누, 폰디움으로 운송 가능"
		4 "리벤펠, 응가카누, 폰디움, 테오누이로 운송 가능"
		5|# "리벤펠, 응가카누, 폰디움, 테오누이, 칼구르로 운송 가능"
	lang "Japanese"
	5
		1 "リベン・フェルに輸送できる"
		2 "リベン・フェルおよびナカヌに輸送できる"
		3 "リベン・フェル、ナカヌおよびポンディウムに輸送できる"
		4 "リベン・フェル、ナカヌ、ポンディウムおよびテ・オヌイに輸送できる"
		5|# "リベン・フェル、ナカヌ、ポンディウム、テ・オヌイおよびカルグールに輸送できる"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	5
		1 "可運送至里本丘原"
		2 "可運送至里本丘原和尼加卡努"
		3 "可運送至里本丘原、尼加卡努和龐狄恩"
		4 "可運送至里本丘原、尼加卡努、龐狄恩和特歐努伊"
		5|# "可運送至里本丘原、尼加卡努、龐狄恩、特歐努伊和卡爾葛"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	5	
		1 "可以航向里本费尔"
		2 "可以航向里本费尔和纳玛鲁伊"
		3 "可以航向里本费尔，纳玛鲁伊和庞蒂姆"
		4 "可以航向里本费尔，纳玛鲁伊，庞蒂姆和特奥努伊"
		5|# "可以航向里本费尔，纳玛鲁伊，庞蒂姆，特奥努伊和卡古兰"
	lang "French"
	5
		1 "Peut naviguer jusqu'à Riben Fell"
		2 "Peut naviguer jusqu'à Riben Fell et Ngakanu"
		3 "Peut naviguer jusqu'à Riben Fell, Ngakanu et Pondium"
		4 "Peut naviguer jusqu'à Riben Fell, Ngakanu, Pondium et Te Onui"
		5|# "Peut naviguer jusqu'à Riben Fell, Ngakanu, Pondium, Te Onui et Kalguur"

description
	1 village_can_smith_ores_up_to_rank
	5
		1 "Can Smelt Crimson Iron Ore"
		2 "Can Smelt Crimson Iron and Orichalcum Ores"
		3 "Can Smelt Crimson Iron, Orichalcum and Petrified Amber Ores"
		4 "Can Smelt Crimson Iron, Orichalcum, Petrified Amber and Bismuth Ores"
		5|# "Can Smelt Crimson Iron, Orichalcum, Petrified Amber, Bismuth and Verisium Ores"
	lang "Russian"
	5
		1 "Может переплавлять руду багрового железа"
		2 "Может переплавлять руду багрового железа и орихалковую руду"
		3 "Может переплавлять руду багрового железа, окаменелого янтаря и орихалковую руду"
		4 "Может переплавлять руду багрового железа, окаменелого янтаря, орихалковую и висмутовую руду"
		5|# "Может переплавлять руду багрового железа, окаменелого янтаря, орихалковую, висмутовую и веризиевую руду"
	lang "German"
	5
		1 "Kann Blutrotes Eisenerz verhütten"
		2 "Kann Blutrotes Eisenerz und Oreichalkos Erze verhütten"
		3 "Kann Blutrotes Eisenerz, Oreichalkos und Amberium verhütten"
		4 "Kann Blutrotes Eisenerz, Oreichalkos, Amberium- und Bismuterze verhütten"
		5|# "Kann Blutrotes Eisenerz, Oreichalkos, Amberium-, Bismut- und Verisiumerze verhütten"
	lang "Spanish"
	5
		1 "Puedes fundir mineral de hierro carmesí"
		2 "Puedes fundir mineral de hierro carmesí y oricalco"
		3 "Puedes fundir mineral de hierro carmesí, oricalco y ámbar petrificado"
		4 "Puedes fundir mineral de hierro carmesí, oricalco, ámbar petrificado y bismuto"
		5|# "Puedes fundir mineral de hierro carmesí, oricalco, ámbar petrificado, bismuto y verisium"
	lang "Thai"
	5
		1 "ถลุง แร่เหล็กเลือดนก ได้"
		2 "ถลุง แร่เหล็กเลือดนกและโอริคัลคุม ได้"
		3 "ถลุง แร่เหล็กเลือดนก, โอริคัลคุม, หินอำพัน ได้"
		4 "ถลุง แร่เหล็กเลือดนก, โอริคัลคุม, หินอำพัน, บิสมัท ได้"
		5|# "ถลุง แร่เหล็กเลือดนก, โอริคัลคุม, หินอำพัน, บิสมัท, เวรีเซียม ได้"
	lang "Korean"
	5
		1 "진홍철 광석 제련 가능"
		2 "진홍철, 오리칼쿰 광석 제련 가능"
		3 "진홍철, 오리칼쿰, 석화 호박 광석 제련 가능"
		4 "진홍철, 오리칼쿰, 석화 호박, 비스무트 광석 제련 가능"
		5|# "진홍철, 오리칼쿰, 석화 호박, 비스무트, 베리시움 광석 제련 가능"
	lang "Japanese"
	5
		1 "クリムゾンアイアン鉱石を製錬できる"
		2 "クリムゾンアイアン鉱石およびオリハルコン鉱石を製錬できる"
		3 "クリムゾンアイアン鉱石、オリハルコン鉱石および石化琥珀鉱石を製錬できる"
		4 "クリムゾンアイアン鉱石、オリハルコン鉱石、石化琥珀鉱石およびビスマス鉱石を製錬できる"
		5|# "クリムゾンアイアン鉱石、オリハルコン鉱石、石化琥珀鉱石、ビスマス鉱石およびヴェリシウム鉱石を製錬できる"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	5
		1 "可冶煉緋紅鍛鐵礦材"
		2 "可冶煉緋紅鍛鐵和山銅礦材"
		3 "可冶煉緋紅鍛鐵、山銅和石化琥珀礦材"
		4 "可冶煉緋紅鍛鐵、山銅、石化琥珀和鉍礦材"
		5|# "可冶煉緋紅鍛鐵、山銅、石化琥珀、鉍和維里西姆礦材"
	lang "Portuguese"
	5
		1 "Pode Derreter Minério de Ferro Carmesim"
		2 "Pode Derreter Minério de Ferro Carmesim e Oricálco"
		3 "Pode Derreter Minério de Ferro Carmesim, Oricálco e Âmbares Petrificados"
		4 "Pode Derreter Minério de Ferro Carmesim, Oricálco, Âmbares Petrificados e Bismuto"
		5|# "Pode Derreter Minério de Ferro Carmesim, Oricálco, Âmbares Petrificados, Bismuto e Verísio"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	5
		1 "可以冶炼绯红铁矿石"
		2 "可以冶炼绯红铁矿石和奥利哈刚矿石"
		3 "可以冶炼绯红铁矿石，奥利哈刚矿石和石化琥珀矿石"
		4 "可以冶炼绯红铁矿石，奥利哈刚矿石，石化琥珀矿石和铋矿石"
		5|# "可以冶炼绯红铁矿石，奥利哈刚矿石，石化琥珀矿石，铋矿石和维金矿石"
	lang "French"
	5
		1 "Peut Fondre du Minerai de Fer écarlate"
		2 "Peut Fondre du Minerai de Fer écarlate et Orichalque"
		3 "Peut Fondre du Minerai de Fer écarlate, Orichalque et Ambre pétrifié"
		4 "Peut Fondre du Minerai de Fer écarlate, Orichalque, Ambre pétrifié et Bismuth"
		5|# "Peut Fondre du Minerai de Fer écarlate, Orichalque, Ambre pétrifié, Bismuth et Vérisium"

description
	1 village_disenchant_value_+%_per_corrupted_implicit
	2
		1|# "{}% increased Thaumaturgic Dust per Corruption Implicit"
		#|-1 "{}% reduced Thaumaturgic Dust per Corruption Implicit" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Cantidad de polvo taumatúrgico aumentada un {}% por cada implícito de corrupción"
		#|-1 "Cantidad de polvo taumatúrgico reducida un {}% por cada implícito de corrupción" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "コラプト暗黙1個ごとにソーマタージーダストの量が{}%増加する"
		#|-1 "コラプト暗黙1個ごとにソーマタージーダストの量が{}%減少する" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "{}% erhöhter Thaumaturgischer Staub pro verderbtem impliziten Modifikator"
		#|-1 "{}% verringerter Thaumaturgischer Staub pro verderbtem impliziten Modifikator" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "타락 고정 속성 하나당 마석학 가루 {}% 증가"
		#|-1 "타락 고정 속성 하나당 마석학 가루 {}% 감소" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Pó Taumatúrgico aumentada em {}% por Implícito Corrompido"
		#|-1 "Pó Taumatúrgico reduzida em {}% por Implícito Corrompido" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "เพิ่มผงมนต์มณี {}% ต่อจำนวน ม็อดแฝงมลทิน"
		#|-1 "ลดผงมนต์มณี {}% ต่อจำนวน ม็อดแฝงมลทิน" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "{}% увеличение количества получаемой чародейской пыли за каждое собственное свойство осквернения"
		#|-1 "{}% уменьшение количества получаемой чародейской пыли за каждое собственное свойство осквернения" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "每個汙染固定詞綴增加 {}% 奇術魔塵"
		#|-1 "每個汙染固定詞綴減少 {}% 奇術魔塵" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	2
		1|# "每一种腐化基底使获得的奇术之尘提高 {}%"
		#|-1 "每一种腐化基底使获得的奇术之尘降低 {}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Poussière thaumaturgique par Implicite de Corruption"
		#|-1 "{}% de Réduction de la Poussière thaumaturgique par Implicite de Corruption" negate 1

description
	1 village_disenchant_value_+%_per_influence_type
	2
		1|# "{}% increased Thaumaturgic Dust per Influence Type"
		#|-1 "{}% reduced Thaumaturgic Dust per Influence Type" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Cantidad de polvo taumatúrgico aumentada un {}% por cada tipo de influencia"
		#|-1 "Cantidad de polvo taumatúrgico reducida un {}% por cada tipo de influencia" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "インフルエンスタイプ1種類ごとにソーマタージーダストが{}%増加する"
		#|-1 "インフルエンスタイプ1種類ごとにソーマタージーダストが{}%減少する" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "{}% erhöhter Thaumaturgischer Staub pro Einflusstyp"
		#|-1 "{}% verringerter Thaumaturgischer Staub pro Einflusstyp" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "영향력 유형 하나당 마석학 가루 {}% 증가"
		#|-1 "영향력 유형 하나당 마석학 가루 {}% 감소" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Pó Taumatúrgico aumentada em {}% por Tipo de Influência"
		#|-1 "Pó Taumatúrgico reduzida em {}% por Tipo de Influência" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "เพิ่มผงมนต์มณี {}% ต่อจำนวน ชนิดอิทธิพล"
		#|-1 "ลดผงมนต์มณี {}% ต่อจำนวน ชนิดอิทธิพล" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "{}% увеличение количества получаемой чародейской пыли за каждый тип влияния на предмете"
		#|-1 "{}% уменьшение количества получаемой чародейской пыли за каждый тип влияния на предмете" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "每個勢力類型增加 {}% 奇術魔塵"
		#|-1 "每個勢力類型減少 {}% 奇術魔塵" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	2
		1|# "每一种影响类型使获得的奇术之尘提高 {}%"
		#|-1 "每一种影响类型使获得的奇术之尘降低 {}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Poussière thaumaturgique par type d'Implicite"
		#|-1 "{}% de Réduction de la Poussière thaumaturgique par type d'Implicite" negate 1

description
	1 village_disenchant_value_+%_per_quality
	2
		1|# "{}% increased Thaumaturgic Dust per Item Quality"
		#|-1 "{}% reduced Thaumaturgic Dust per Item Quality" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Cantidad de polvo taumatúrgico aumentada un {}% por cada punto de calidad en el objeto"
		#|-1 "Cantidad de polvo taumatúrgico reducida un {}% por cada punto de calidad en el objeto" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "アイテム品質ごとにソーマタージーダストが{}%増加する"
		#|-1 "アイテム品質ごとにソーマタージーダストが{}%減少する" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "{}% erhöhter Thaumaturgischer Staub pro Gegenstandsqualität"
		#|-1 "{}% verringerter Thaumaturgischer Staub pro Gegenstandsqualität" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "아이템 퀄리티 1당 마석학 가루 {}% 증가"
		#|-1 "아이템 퀄리티 1당 마석학 가루 {}% 감소" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Pó Taumatúrgico aumentada em {}% por Qualidade do Item"
		#|-1 "Pó Taumatúrgico reduzida em {}% por Qualidade do Item" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "เพิ่มผงมนต์มณี {}% ต่อจำนวน ค่าคุณภาพของไอเทม"
		#|-1 "ลดผงมนต์มณี {}% ต่อจำนวน ค่าคุณภาพของไอเทม" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "{}% увеличение количества получаемой чародейской пыли за качество на предмете"
		#|-1 "{}% уменьшение количества получаемой чародейской пыли за качество на предмете" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "每種物品品質增加 {}% 奇術魔塵"
		#|-1 "每種物品品質減少 {}% 奇術魔塵" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	2
		1|# "每一点物品品质使获得的奇术之尘提高 {}%"
		#|-1 "每一点物品品质使获得的奇术之尘降低 {}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Poussière thaumaturgique par Qualité de l'Objet"
		#|-1 "{}% de Réduction de la Poussière thaumaturgique par Qualité de l'Objet" negate 1

description
	1 village_disenchanting_speed_+%
	1
		# "{}% increased Disenchanting Speed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% повышение скорости распыления"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Entzauberungsgeschwindigkeit"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Velocidad de desencantamiento aumentada un {}%"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มความเร็ว สลายไอเทม {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "인챈트 해제 속도 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "エンチャントを解呪するスピードが{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "增加 {}% 破幻速度"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Velocidade de Desencantamento aumentada em {}%"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "分解速度提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Vitesse de Désenchantement"

description
	1 village_farming_speed_+%
	1
		# "{}% increased Farming Speed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% повышение скорости занятия фермерством"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Landwirtschaftsgeschwindigkeit"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Velocidad de cultivo aumentada un {}%"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มความเร็ว เพาะปลูก {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "경작 속도 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "農業のスピードが{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "增加 {}% 耕種速度"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Velocidade de Agricultura aumentada em {}%"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "耕作速度提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Vitesse de l'Agriculture"

description
	1 village_farming_yield_+%_per_adjacent_plot_farmed
	1
		# "Plots yield {}% increased Crop per adjacent Plot being Farmed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% увеличение урожая на участках за каждый обрабатываемый соседний участок"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "Flächen gewähren {}% erhöhte Ernte je angrenzender Fläche, die geerntet wird"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Las parcelas tienen su producción aumentada un {}% por cada parcela adyacente cultivada"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "แปลง ให้ผลผลิตต้นกล้า เพิ่มขึ้น {}% ต่อจำนวนของ แปลงข้างเคียง ที่เพาะปลูก"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "경작 중인 인접 경작지 하나당 경작지 수확량 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "隣接して育てられている農地1か所ごとに農地で生育する作物の量が{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "每有一個被耕種的鄰近農地，增加 {}% 農地作物產量"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Plantações rendem colheita aumentada em {}% por Plantação adjacente sendo Cultivada"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "每耕作一片相邻的耕作田，耕作田的产量提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "Les Parcelles ont {}% d'Augmentation de Récoltes produites par Parcelle adjacente Cultivée"

description
	1 village_farming_yield_+%_per_different_crop_farmed
	1
		# "{}% increased Crop yield per different Crop being Farmed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% увеличение количества собираемого урожая за каждый отдельный тип посевов"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Ernteerträge je unterschiedlicher geernteter Pflanze"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Cosecha aumentada un {}% por cada cultivo diferente que hayas plantado"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มผลผลิตต้นกล้า {}% ต่อจำนวนของ ต้นกล้าที่แตกต่างกัน ที่เพาะปลูก"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "경작 중인 작물 가짓수 하나당 작물 수확량 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "育てられている異なる種類の作物1種類ごとに作物の量が{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "每一塊不同的農地被耕種時，增加 {}% 作物產量"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Rendimento das Plantações aumentado em {}% por Plantação diferente sendo Cultivada"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "每种植一种不同的作物，作物产量提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "{}% d'Augmentation des Récoltes produites par Culture différente Cultivée"

description
	1 village_fishing_speed_+%
	1
		# "{}% increased Fishing Speed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% повышение скорости занятия рыбалкой"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Fischereigeschwindigkeit"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Velocidad de pesca aumentada un {}%"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มความเร็ว ตกปลา {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "낚시 속도 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "漁業のスピードが{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "增加 {}% 釣魚速度"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Velocidade da Pescaria aumentada em {}%"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "钓鱼速度提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "La Pêche a {}% d'Augmentation de Vitesse"

description
	1 village_gold_per_ore_mined
	1
		# "Marking Ore in Areas grants Gold equal to the amount of Ore"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "Das Markieren von Erzen in Gebieten gewährt Gold in Höhe der Erzmenge"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Marcar el mineral en las áreas otorga una cantidad de oro equivalente a la cantidad de mineral"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "การยึดครองแร่ในด่านจะให้ ทอง เท่ากับ จำนวนของแร่"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "지역 내 광석에 표시를 하면 광석의 양과 동일한 골드 획득"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Marcar Minérios nas Áreas concede Ouro igual a quantidade de Minério"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "Отметка руды в областях дает золото, равное количеству руды"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "エリアで鉱石をマーキングすると鉱石の量と同量のゴールドを付与する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "標記區域內的礦材可獲得相當於礦材數量的金幣"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	1
		# "区域内标记的矿脉提供与矿石等量的金币"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "Marquer du Minerai dans les Zones octroie de l'Or équivalent à la quantité de Minerai"

description
	1 village_idol_gambling
	1
		1|# "Faustus offers Idols at the Black Market"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	1
		1|# "浮士德会在黑市为你提供雕像"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		1|# "ファースタスが闇市場でアイドルを販売する"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		1|# "Faustus ofrece ídolos en el mercado negro"
	lang "French"
	1
		1|# "Faustus propose des Idoles au Marché noir"
	lang "German"
	1
		1|# "Faustus bietet Götzen auf dem Schwarzmarkt an"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		1|# "Faustus Oferece Ídolos no Mercado Negro"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		1|# "Фауст предлагает идолы на чёрном рынке"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		1|# "ฟาวทัส เสนอ เทวรูป ที่ตลาดมืด"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		1|# "파우스투스가 암시장에서 우상 제시"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		1|# "弗斯特在黑市提供魔偶"

description
	1 village_mapping_speed_+%
	1
		# "{}% increased Mapping Speed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% повышение скорости исследования карт"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Kartenlauf-Geschwindigkeit"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Velocidad de exploración aumentada un {}%"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มความเร็ว บุกแผนที่ {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "지도 탐험 속도 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "マッピングスピードが{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "增加 {}% 刷圖速度"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Velocidade do Mapeamento aumentada em {}%"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "异界冒险速度提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Vitesse d'Exploration des Cartes"

description
	1 village_maps_have_mod_effect_+%
	2
		1|# "{0}% increased effect of Explicit Modifiers on Maps"
		#|-1 "{0}% reduced effect of Explicit Modifiers on Maps" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Efeito dos Modificadores Explícitos dos Mapas aumentado em {0}%"
		#|-1 "Efeito dos Modificadores Explícitos dos Mapas reduzido em {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "地圖上的變動詞綴效果增加 {0}%"
		#|-1 "地圖上的變動詞綴效果減少 {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "지도에 적용되는 비고정 속성의 효과 {0}% 증가"
		#|-1 "지도에 적용되는 비고정 속성의 효과 {0}% 감소" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "{0}% erhöhte Wirkung von expliziten Modifikatoren auf Karten"
		#|-1 "{0}% verringerte Wirkung von expliziten Modifikatoren auf Karten" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "{0}% усиление эффекта добавленных свойств на картах"
		#|-1 "{0}% ослабление эффекта добавленных свойств на картах" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "เพิ่มผลของ ม็อดหลัก ของแผนที่ {0}%"
		#|-1 "ลดผลของ ม็อดหลัก ของแผนที่ {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "マップの明示モッドの効果が{0}%増加する"
		#|-1 "マップの明示モッドの効果が{0}%減少する" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Efecto de los modificadores explícitos de los mapas aumentado un {0}%"
		#|-1 "Efecto de los modificadores explícitos de los mapas reducido un {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1|# "地图的外延词缀效果提高 {0}%"
		#|-1 "地图的外延词缀效果降低 {0}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "{0}% d'Augmentation de l'Effet des Modificateurs Explicites sur les Cartes"
		#|-1 "{0}% de Réduction de l'Effet des Modificateurs Explicites sur les Cartes" negate 1

description
	1 village_max_crew_per_ship
	2
		1 "{0} Maximum Ship Crew"
		2|# "{0} Maximum Ship Crew"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Максимум членов экипажа: {0}"
		2|# "Максимум членов экипажа: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Maximal {0} Besatzungsmitglied"
		2|# "Maximal {0} Besatzungsmitglieder"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Máximo de tripulantes de barco: {0}"
		2|# "Máximo de tripulantes de barco: {0}"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "มี ลูกเรือ ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
		2|# "มี ลูกเรือ ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "선원 최대 {0}명"
		2|# "선원 최대 {0}명"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "船の乗組員の最大数 {0}"
		2|# "船の乗組員の最大数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 船員上限"
		2|# "{0} 船員上限"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} ao Máximo de Marinheiros"
		2|# "{0} ao Máximo de Marinheiros"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 船员上限"
		2|# "{0} 船员上限"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Membre d'équipage au maximum"
		2|# "{0} Membres d'équipage au maximum"

description
	1 village_max_farmers_per_plot
	2
		1 "{0} Maximum Farmer per Plot"
		2|# "{0} Maximum Farmers per Plot"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Максимум фермеров на участок: {0}"
		2|# "Максимум фермеров на участок: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Maximal {0} Landwirt pro Anbaufläche"
		2|# "Maximal {0} Landwirte pro Anbaufläche"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Máximo de agricultores por cada parcela: {0}"
		2|# "Máximo de agricultores por cada parcela: {0}"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "มี ชาวไร่ ได้สูงสุด {0} คนต่อแปลง"
		2|# "มี ชาวไร่ ได้สูงสุด {0} คนต่อแปลง"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "경작지당 농부 최대 {0}명"
		2|# "경작지당 농부 최대 {0}명"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "農地ごとの農民の最大数 {0}"
		2|# "農地ごとの農民の最大数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 每個農地農夫上限"
		2|# "{0} 每個農地農夫上限"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} ao Máximo de Fazendeiros por Plantação"
		2|# "{0} ao Máximo de Fazendeiros por Plantação"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 每片耕作田的农夫上限"
		2|# "{0} 每片耕作田的农夫上限"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Fermier au maximum par Parcelle"
		2|# "{0} Fermiers au maximum par Parcelle"

description
	1 village_max_mappers_per_device
	2
		1 "Map Devices have {0} Portal"
		2|# "Map Devices have {0} Portals"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Машина картоходца открывает порталов: {0}"
		2|# "Машина картоходца открывает порталов: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Kartenapparate haben {0} Portal"
		2|# "Kartenapparate haben {0} Portale"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Los artefactos de mapas tienen {0} portal"
		2|# "Los artefactos de mapas tienen {0} portales"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "เครื่องเปิดแผนที่ มีวาร์ป {0} แห่ง"
		2|# "เครื่องเปิดแผนที่ มีวาร์ป {0} แห่ง"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "지도 장치로 열리는 포탈 {0}개"
		2|# "지도 장치로 열리는 포탈 {0}개"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "マップデバイスのポータル数 {0}"
		2|# "マップデバイスのポータル数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "地圖裝置有 {0} 個時空之門"
		2|# "地圖裝置有 {0} 個時空之門"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "Dispositivos de Mapa têm {0} Portal"
		2|# "Dispositivos de Mapa têm {0} Portais"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "地图装置具有 {0} 个传送门"
		2|# "地图装置具有 {0} 个传送门"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "Les Dispositifs cartographiques ont {0} Portail"
		2|# "Les Dispositifs cartographiques ont {0} Portails"

description
	1 village_max_number_of_disenchanters
	2
		1 "{0} Maximum Disenchanter"
		2|# "{0} Maximum Disenchanters"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Максимум распылителей: {0}"
		2|# "Максимум распылителей: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Maximal {0} Entzauberer"
		2|# "Maximal {0} Entzauberer"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Máximo de desencantadores: {0}"
		2|# "Máximo de desencantadores: {0}"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "มี นักสลายไอเทม ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
		2|# "มี นักสลายไอเทม ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "인챈트 해제사 최대 {0}명"
		2|# "인챈트 해제사 최대 {0}명"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "解呪師の最大数 {0}"
		2|# "解呪師の最大数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 破幻者上限"
		2|# "{0} 破幻者上限"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} ao Máximo de Desencantadores"
		2|# "{0} ao Máximo de Desencantadores"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 分解师上限"
		2|# "{0} 分解师上限"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Désenchanteur au maximum"
		2|# "{0} Désenchanteurs au maximum"

description
	1 village_max_number_of_fishers
	2
		1 "{0} Maximum Fisherman"
		2|# "{0} Maximum Fishermen"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Максимум рыбаков: {0}"
		2|# "Максимум рыбаков: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Maximal {0} Fischer"
		2|# "Maximal {0} Fischer"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Máximo de pescadores: {0}"
		2|# "Máximo de pescadores: {0}"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "มี ชาวประมง ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
		2|# "มี ชาวประมง ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "어부 최대 {0}명"
		2|# "어부 최대 {0}명"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "釣り人の最大数 {0}"
		2|# "釣り人の最大数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 漁夫上限"
		2|# "{0} 漁夫上限"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} ao Máximo de Pescadores"
		2|# "{0} ao Máximo de Pescadores"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 渔夫上限"
		2|# "{0} 渔夫上限"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Pêcheur au maximum"
		2|# "{0} Pêcheurs au maximum"

description
	1 village_max_number_of_miners
	2
		1 "{0} Maximum Miner"
		2|# "{0} Maximum Miners"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Максимум шахтеров: {0}"
		2|# "Максимум шахтеров: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Maximal {0} Bergbauer"
		2|# "Maximal {0} Bergbauern"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Máximo de mineros: {0}"
		2|# "Máximo de mineros: {0}"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "มี คนขุดแร่ ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
		2|# "มี คนขุดแร่ ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "광부 최대 {0}명"
		2|# "광부 최대 {0}명"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "鉱夫の最大数 {0}"
		2|# "鉱夫の最大数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 礦工上限"
		2|# "{0} 礦工上限"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} ao Máximo de Mineiros"
		2|# "{0} ao Máximo de Mineiros"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 矿工上限"
		2|# "{0} 矿工上限"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Mineur au maximum"
		2|# "{0} Mineurs au maximum"

description
	1 village_max_number_of_smiths
	2
		1 "{0} Maximum Smelter"
		2|# "{0} Maximum Smelters"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Максимум плавильщиков: {0}"
		2|# "Максимум плавильщиков: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Maximal {0} Schmelzer"
		2|# "Maximal {0} Schmelzer"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Máximo de fundidores: {0}"
		2|# "Máximo de fundidores: {0}"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "มี ช่างถลุง ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
		2|# "มี ช่างถลุง ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "제련가 최대 {0}명"
		2|# "제련가 최대 {0}명"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "製錬者の最大数 {0}"
		2|# "製錬者の最大数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 冶煉者上限"
		2|# "{0} 冶煉者上限"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} ao Máximo de Fundidores"
		2|# "{0} ao Máximo de Fundidores"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 冶炼师上限"
		2|# "{0} 冶炼师上限"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Fondeur au maximum"
		2|# "{0} Fondeurs au maximum"

description
	1 village_max_number_of_workers
	2
		1 "{0} Maximum Town Population"
		2|# "{0} Maximum Town Population"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Максимум горожан: {0}"
		2|# "Максимум горожан: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Maximale Stadtbevölkerung: {0}"
		2|# "Maximale Stadtbevölkerung: {0}"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "Población máxima del pueblo: {0}"
		2|# "Población máxima del pueblo: {0}"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "มี ประชากรเมือง ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
		2|# "มี ประชากรเมือง ได้สูงสุด {0} คน"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "마을 인구 최대 {0}명"
		2|# "마을 인구 최대 {0}명"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "街の人口の最大数 {0}"
		2|# "街の人口の最大数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 城鎮人口上限"
		2|# "{0} 城鎮人口上限"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} ao Máximo de População da Cidade"
		2|# "{0} ao Máximo de População da Cidade"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 城镇人口上限"
		2|# "{0} 城镇人口上限"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "La Ville a une Population maximum de {0}"
		2|# "La Ville a une Population maximum de {0}"

description
	1 village_mining_speed_+%
	1
		# "{}% increased Mining Speed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% повышение скорости занятия горным делом"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Bergbaugeschwindigkeit"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Velocidad de extracción aumentada un {}%"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มความเร็ว ขุดแร่ {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "채광 속도 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "採掘スピードが{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "增加 {}% 開採速度"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Velocidade da Mineração aumentada em {}%"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "采掘速度提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "Le Minage a {}% d'Augmentation de Vitesse"

description
	1 village_number_of_farm_plots
	2
		1 "{0} Farming Plot"
		2|# "{0} Farming Plots"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Фермерских участков: {0}"
		2|# "Фермерских участков: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "{0} Anbaufläche"
		2|# "{0} Anbauflächen"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "{0} parcela de cultivo"
		2|# "{0} parcelas de cultivo"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "แปลงเพาะปลูก {0} แปลง"
		2|# "แปลงเพาะปลูก {0} แปลง"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "경작지 {0}개"
		2|# "경작지 {0}개"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "農地の数 {0}"
		2|# "農地の数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 農地"
		2|# "{0} 農地"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} Plantação"
		2|# "{0} Plantações"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 片耕作田"
		2|# "{0} 片耕作田"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Parcelle de culture"
		2|# "{0} Parcelles de culture"

description
	1 village_number_of_map_devices
	2
		1 "{0} Map Device"
		2|# "{0} Map Devices"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Машин картоходца: {0}"
		2|# "Машин картоходца: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "{0} Kartenapparat"
		2|# "{0} Kartenapparate"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "{0} artefacto de mapas"
		2|# "{0} artefactos de mapas"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "เครื่องเปิดแผนที่ {0} เครื่อง"
		2|# "เครื่องเปิดแผนที่ {0} เครื่อง"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "지도 장치 {0}개"
		2|# "지도 장치 {0}개"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "マップデバイス数 {0}"
		2|# "マップデバイス数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 個地圖裝置"
		2|# "{0} 個地圖裝置"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} Dispositivo de Mapas"
		2|# "{0} Dispositivos de Mapas"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 个地图装置"
		2|# "{0} 个地图装置"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Dispositif cartographique"
		2|# "{0} Dispositifs cartographiques"

description
	1 village_number_of_recruits
	2
		1 "Recruitment Agency lists up to {0} Recruit"
		2|# "Recruitment Agency lists up to {0} Recruits"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "В агентстве найма отображается рекрутов:{0}"
		2|# "В агентстве найма отображается рекрутов:{0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "Rekrutierungsstelle listet bis zu {0} Rekruten"
		2|# "Rekrutierungsstelle listet bis zu {0} Rekruten"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "La agencia de reclutamiento muestra hasta {0} recluta"
		2|# "La agencia de reclutamiento muestra hasta {0} reclutas"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "ตัวแทนการเกณฑ์แรงงาน ลงรายชื่อ แรงงานเกณฑ์ สูงสุด {0} คน"
		2|# "ตัวแทนการเกณฑ์แรงงาน ลงรายชื่อ แรงงานเกณฑ์ สูงสุด {0} คน"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "모집 중개소가 최대 {0}명의 신입 소개"
		2|# "모집 중개소가 최대 {0}명의 신입 소개"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "人材紹介所は最大 {0}人の募集人員を紹介する"
		2|# "人材紹介所は最大 {0}人の募集人員を紹介する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "召募人最多列出 {0} 個新人"
		2|# "召募人最多列出 {0} 個新人"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "Agência de Recrutamento lista até {0} Recruta"
		2|# "Agência de Recrutamento lista até {0} Recrutas"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "招募经纪人会列出最多 {0} 个人选"
		2|# "招募经纪人会列出最多 {0} 个人选"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "L'Agence de recrutement a une liste de {0} Recrue au maximum"
		2|# "L'Agence de recrutement a une liste de {0} Recrues au maximum"

description
	1 village_number_of_ships
	2
		1 "{0} Ship"
		2|# "{0} Ships"
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1 "Кораблей: {0}"
		2|# "Кораблей: {0}"
	lang "German"
	2
		1 "{0} Schiff"
		2|# "{0} Schiffe"
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1 "{0} barco"
		2|# "{0} barcos"
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1 "เรือ {0} ลำ"
		2|# "เรือ {0} ลำ"
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1 "선박 {0}척"
		2|# "선박 {0}척"
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1 "船の数 {0}"
		2|# "船の数 {0}"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1 "{0} 艘船隻"
		2|# "{0} 艘船隻"
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1 "{0} Navio"
		2|# "{0} Navios"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1 "{0} 条船只"
		2|# "{0} 条船只"
	lang "French"
	2
		1 "{0} Navire"
		2|# "{0} Navires"

description
	1 village_ore_found_+%
	2
		1|# "{0}% increased Ore found in Areas"
		#|-1 "{0}% reduced Ore found in Areas" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Minério Encontrado nas Áreas aumentado em {0}%"
		#|-1 "Minério Encontrado nas Áreas reduzido em {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "เพิ่ม แร่ ที่พบในด่าน {0}%"
		#|-1 "ลด แร่ ที่พบในด่าน {0}%" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "{0}% erhöhte Menge von gefundenem Erz in Gebieten"
		#|-1 "{0}% verringerte Menge von gefundenem Erz in Gebieten" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "{0}% увеличение количества находимой в областях руды"
		#|-1 "{0}% увеличение количества находимой в областях руды" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Cantidad de minerales encontrados en las áreas aumentada un {0}%"
		#|-1 "Cantidad de minerales encontrados en las áreas reducida un {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "지역에서 발견하는 광석 {0}% 증가"
		#|-1 "지역에서 발견하는 광석 {0}% 감소" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "エリアで見つかる鉱石の量が{0}%増加する"
		#|-1 "エリアで見つかる鉱石の量が{0}%減少する" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "增加 {0}% 區域內發現的礦材"
		#|-1 "減少 {0}% 區域內發現的礦材" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	2
		1|# "该区域内找到的矿石数量提高 {0}%"
		#|-1 "该区域内找到的地图数量降低 {0}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "{0}% d'Augmentation du Minerai trouvé dans les Zones"
		#|-1 "{0}% de Réduction du Minerai trouvé dans les Zones" negate 1

description
	1 village_port_quota_effectiveness_+%
	2
		1|# "Ports Quotas are {}% more rewarding"
		#|-1 "Ports Quotas are {}% less rewarding" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Quotas dos Portos são {}% mais recompensadoras"
		#|-1 "Quotas dos Portos são {}% menos recompensadoras" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "港口配額給予的獎勵增加 {}%"
		#|-1 "港口配額給予的獎勵減少 {}%" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "항만 할당량 보상 {}% 증폭"
		#|-1 "항만 할당량 보상 {}% 감폭" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "Hafenquoten sind {}% lohnender"
		#|-1 "Hafenquoten sind {}% weniger lohnend" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "Выполнение требований портов приносит на {}% больше наград"
		#|-1 "Выполнение требований портов приносит на {}% меньше наград" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "โควต้าเมืองท่า ให้ของรางวัล เพิ่มขึ้น อีก {}%"
		#|-1 "โควต้าเมืองท่า ให้ของรางวัล ลดลง อีก {}%" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "港の受付制限量の報酬が{}%上昇する"
		#|-1 "港の受付制限量の報酬が{}%低下する" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Las cuotas de puerto ofrecen un {}% más de recompensas"
		#|-1 "Las cuotas de puerto ofrecen un {}% menos de recompensas" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1|# "港口定额的奖励总增 {}%"
		#|-1 "港口定额的奖励总降 {}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "Les Quotas des Ports ont {}% Davantage de Générosité"
		#|-1 "Les Quotas des Ports ont {}% de Perte de Générosité" negate 1

description
	1 village_rarer_ores_found
	1
		# "Ores found in Areas are more likely to be rarer varieties"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Los minerales que encuentres en las áreas tienen mayor probabilidad de ser de variedades más raras"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "エリアで見つかる鉱石はより高い確率で珍しい種類になる"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "In Gebieten gefundene Erze gehören mit größerer Wahrscheinlichkeit selteneren Typen an"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "지역 내에서 발견하는 광석이 보다 희귀한 종류일 확률이 높아짐"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Minérios encontrados nas Áreas são mais propensos a serem de variedades mais raras"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "แร่ ที่พบในด่าน มีโอกาสเป็น ลักษณะที่พบได้ยากกว่าเดิม มากขึ้น"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "Найденная в областях руда с большей вероятностью будет более редких видов"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "區域內發現的礦材有更高機率為更稀有的種類"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	1
		# "区域内的矿石更有可能为稀有类型"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "Le Minerai trouvé dans les Zones est plus susceptible d'être plus rare"

description
	1 village_recombination_chance_to_upgrade_modifier_tier_%
	1
		# "{}% chance for Modifiers to upgrade tier"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% шанс для свойств повысить свой уровень"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% Chance für Modifikatoren, um einen Level aufgewertet zu werden"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "{}% de probabilidad de que se mejore el grado de los modificadores"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "ม็อด มีโอกาสเพิ่มอันดับ {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "{}% 확률로 속성 등급 업그레이드"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "{}%の確率でモッドはティアをアップグレードする"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "詞綴有 {}% 機率提升階級"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "{}% de chance de Modificadores subirem de tier"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "{}% 的几率将词缀升级"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "{}% de chances que le Palier des Modificateurs soit plus élevé"

description
	1 village_recombination_rarer_mods_more_likely_to_be_retained
	1
		# "Rarer Modifiers are more likely to be retained"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "Более редкие свойства с большей вероятностью будут сохранены"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "Seltene Modifikatoren werden mit größerer Wahrscheinlichkeit beibehalten"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Es más probable que se conserven los modificadores más raros"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "ม็อดที่พบได้ยากกว่าเดิม มีโอกาสรักษาเอาไว้มากกว่าเดิม"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "희귀도가 높은 속성일수록 유지될 확률이 높아짐"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "よりレアなモッドがより高い確率で維持される"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "較稀有的詞綴有更高的機率被保留"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Modificadores Raros são mais propensos a serem retidos"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "高稀有度词缀更有可能被保留"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "Les Modificateurs Rares ont plus de chances d'être conservés"

description
	1 village_recombinator_cost_+%
	2
		1|# "{}% increased Recombination Cost"
		#|-1 "{}% reduced Recombination Cost" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "{}% повышение стоимости рекомбинации"
		#|-1 "{}% снижение стоимости рекомбинации" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "{}% erhöhte Rekombinationskosten"
		#|-1 "{}% verringerte Rekombinationskosten" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Costo de la recombinación aumentado un {}%"
		#|-1 "Costo de la recombinación reducido un {}%" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "เพิ่มค่าผสมไอเทม {}%"
		#|-1 "ลดค่าผสมไอเทม {}%" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "재조합 비용 {}% 증가"
		#|-1 "재조합 비용 {}% 감소" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "リコンビネートのコストが{}%増加する"
		#|-1 "リコンビネートのコストが{}%減少する" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "增加 {}% 重組消耗"
		#|-1 "減少 {}% 重組消耗" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Custo da Recombinação aumentado em {}%"
		#|-1 "Custo da Recombinação reduzido em {}%" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1|# "重组成本提高 {}%"
		#|-1 "重组成本降低 {}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "La Recombination a {}% d'Augmentation de Coût"
		#|-1 "La Recombination a {}% de Réduction de Coût" negate 1

description
	1 village_recruit_cost_+%
	2
		1|# "{0}% increased Recruitment Reroll Cost"
		#|-1 "{0}% reduced Recruitment Reroll Cost" negate 1
	lang "Russian"
	2
		1|# "{0}% повышение стоимости обновления списка наймов"
		#|-1 "{0}% снижение стоимости обновления списка наймов" negate 1
	lang "German"
	2
		1|# "{0}% erhöhte Kosten für das Rekrutierungs-Neuwürfeln"
		#|-1 "{0}% verringerte Kosten für das Rekrutierungs-Neuwürfeln" negate 1
	lang "Spanish"
	2
		1|# "Costo de aleatorizar a los reclutas aumentado un {0}%"
		#|-1 "Costo de aleatorizar a los reclutas reducido un {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Thai"
	2
		1|# "เพิ่มค่าสุ่มแรงงานเกณฑ์ {0}%"
		#|-1 "ลดค่าสุ่มแรงงานเกณฑ์ {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Korean"
	2
		1|# "신입 무작위 변경 비용 {0}% 증가"
		#|-1 "신입 무작위 변경 비용 {0}% 감소" negate 1
	lang "Japanese"
	2
		1|# "募集人員リロールコストが{0}%増加する"
		#|-1 "募集人員リロールコストが{0}%減少する" negate 1
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	2
		1|# "增加 {0}% 召募重骰消耗"
		#|-1 "減少 {0}% 召募重骰消耗" negate 1
	lang "Portuguese"
	2
		1|# "Custo de Rolagem do Recrutamento aumentado em {0}%"
		#|-1 "Custo de Rolagem do Recrutamento reduzido em {0}%" negate 1
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	2	
		1|# "招募重置成本提高 {0}%"
		#|-1 "招募重置成本降低 {0}%" negate 1
	lang "French"
	2
		1|# "Le Recrutement a {0}% d'Augmentation du Coût d'un Nouveau tirage"
		#|-1 "Le Recrutement a {0}% de Réduction du Coût d'un Nouveau tirage" negate 1

description
	1 village_runesmithing_runes
	10
		1 "Can Runesmith using Sun Runes"
		2 "Can Runesmith using Sun and Bound Runes"
		3 "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound and Life Runes"
		4 "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound, Life and War Runes"
		5 "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound, Life, War and River Runes"
		6 "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound, Life, War, River and Bounty Runes"
		7 "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound, Life, War, River, Bounty and Journey Runes"
		8 "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound, Life, War, River, Bounty, Journey and Mountain Runes"
		9 "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound, Life, War, River, Bounty, Journey, Mountain and Time Runes"
		10|# "Can Runesmith using Sun, Bound, Life, War, River, Bounty, Journey, Mountain, Time and Power Runes"
	lang "Portuguese"
	10
		1 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares"
		2 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares e Limitantes"
		3 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes e Vitais"
		4 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes, Vitais e Bélicas"
		5 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes, Vitais, Bélicas e Fluviais"
		6 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes, Vitais, Bélicas, Fluviais e Recompensadoras"
		7 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes, Vitais, Bélicas, Fluviais, Recompensadoras e Viajantes"
		8 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes, Vitais, Bélicas, Fluviais, Recompensadoras, Viajantes e Montícolas"
		9 "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes, Vitais, Bélicas, Fluviais, Recompensadoras, Viajantes, Montícolas e Temporais"
		10|# "Pode usar Runologia com Runas Solares, Limitantes, Vitais, Bélicas, Fluviais, Recompensadoras, Viajantes, Montícolas, Temporais e Poderosas"
	lang "Thai"
	10
		1 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน ได้"
		2 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวันและตรึง ได้"
		3 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต ได้"
		4 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต, สงคราม ได้"
		5 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต, สงคราม, แม่น้ำ ได้"
		6 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต, สงคราม, แม่น้ำ, มั่งมี ได้"
		7 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต, สงคราม, แม่น้ำ, มั่งมี, สัญจร ได้"
		8 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต, สงคราม, แม่น้ำ, มั่งมี, สัญจร, ขุนเขา ได้"
		9 "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต, สงคราม, แม่น้ำ, มั่งมี, สัญจร, ขุนเขา, กาลเวลา ได้"
		10|# "สลักด้วย อักขระตะวัน, ตรึง, ชีวิต, สงคราม, แม่น้ำ, มั่งมี, สัญจร, ขุนเขา, กาลเวลา, พลัง ได้"
	lang "German"
	10
		1 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnenrunen"
		2 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnenrunen und Bindungsrunen"
		3 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs- und Lebensrunen"
		4 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs-, Lebens- und Kriegsrunen"
		5 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs-, Lebens- und Kriegsrunen"
		6 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs-, Lebens-, Kriegs- und Gabenrunen"
		7 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs-, Lebens-, Kriegs-, Gaben- und Reiserunen"
		8 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs-, Lebens-, Kriegs-, Gaben-, Reise- und Bergrunen"
		9 "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs-, Lebens-, Kriegs-, Gaben-, Reise-, Berg- und Zeitrunen"
		10|# "Kann Runenschmieden unter Nutzung von Sonnen-, Bindungs-, Lebens-, Kriegs-, Gaben-, Reise-, Berg-, Zeit- und Machtrunen"
	lang "Russian"
	10
		1 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца"
		2 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца и Единства"
		3 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства и Жизни"
		4 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства, Жизни и Войны"
		5 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства, Жизни, Войны и Реки"
		6 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства, Жизни, Войны, Реки и Щедрости"
		7 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства, Жизни, Войны, Реки, Щедрости и Странствия"
		8 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства, Жизни, Войны, Реки, Щедрости, Странствия и Горы"
		9 "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства, Жизни, Войны, Реки, Щедрости, Странствия, Горы и Времени"
		10|# "Может использовать в рунном деле руны Солнца, Единства, Жизни, Войны, Реки, Щедрости, Странствия, Горы, Времени и Силы"
	lang "Spanish"
	10
		1 "Puedes usar runas de sol para forjar runas"
		2 "Puedes usar runas de sol y vinculación para forjar runas"
		3 "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación y vida para forjar runas"
		4 "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación, vida y guerra para forjar runas"
		5 "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación, vida, guerra y río para forjar runas"
		6 "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación, vida, guerra, río y botín para forjar runas"
		7 "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación, vida, guerra, río, botín y viaje para forjar runas"
		8 "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación, vida, guerra, río, botín, viaje y montaña para forjar runas"
		9 "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación, vida, guerra, río, botín, viaje, montaña y tiempo para forjar runas"
		10|# "Puedes usar runas de sol, vinculación, vida, guerra, río, botín, viaje, montaña, tiempo y poder para forjar runas"
	lang "Korean"
	10
		1 "태양 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		2 "태양 및 속박 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		3 "태양, 속박, 생명 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		4 "태양, 속박, 생명, 전쟁 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		5 "태양, 속박, 생명, 전쟁, 강 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		6 "태양, 속박, 생명, 전쟁, 강, 하사품 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		7 "태양, 속박, 생명, 전쟁, 강, 하사품, 여정 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		8 "태양, 속박, 생명, 전쟁, 강, 하사품, 여정, 산 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		9 "태양, 속박, 생명, 전쟁, 강, 하사품, 여정, 산, 시간 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
		10|# "태양, 속박, 생명, 전쟁, 강, 하사품, 여정, 산, 시간, 권능 룬으로 룬 제작 가능"
	lang "Japanese"
	10
		1 "日のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		2 "日のルーンおよび賜のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		3 "日のルーン、縛のルーンおよび命のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		4 "日のルーン、縛のルーン、命のルーンおよび戦のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		5 "日のルーン、縛のルーン、命のルーン、戦のルーンおよび川のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		6 "日のルーン、縛のルーン、命のルーン、戦のルーン、川のルーンおよび賜のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		7 "日のルーン、縛のルーン、命のルーン、戦のルーン、川のルーン、賜のルーンおよび旅のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		8 "日のルーン、縛のルーン、命のルーン、戦のルーン、川のルーン、賜のルーン、旅のルーンおよび山のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		9 "日のルーン、縛のルーン、命のルーン、戦のルーン、川のルーン、賜のルーン、旅のルーン、山のルーンおよび時のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
		10|# "日のルーン、縛のルーン、命のルーン、戦のルーン、川のルーン、賜のルーン、旅のルーン、山のルーン、時のルーンおよび力のルーンをルーンスミスに使用できる"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	10
		1 "可使用太陽符文進行魔符鍛造"
		2 "可使用太陽和邊界符文進行魔符鍛造"
		3 "可使用太陽、邊界和生命符文進行魔符鍛造"
		4 "可使用太陽、邊界、生命和戰爭符文進行魔符鍛造"
		5 "可使用太陽、邊界、生命、戰爭和河川符文進行魔符鍛造"
		6 "可使用太陽、邊界、生命、戰爭、河川和寶藏符文進行魔符鍛造"
		7 "可使用太陽、邊界、生命、戰爭、河川、寶藏和旅途符文進行魔符鍛造"
		8 "可使用太陽、邊界、生命、戰爭、河川、寶藏、旅途和山脊符文進行魔符鍛造"
		9 "可使用太陽、邊界、生命、戰爭、河川、寶藏、旅途、山脊和時間符文進行魔符鍛造"
		10|# "可使用太陽、邊界、生命、戰爭、河川、寶藏、旅途、山脊、時間和能量符文進行魔符鍛造"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	10	
		1 "符文匠可以使用太阳符文"
		2 "符文匠可以使用太阳和束缚符文"
		3 "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚和生命符文"
		4 "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚，生命和战争符文"
		5 "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚，生命，战争和河川符文"
		6 "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚，生命，战争，河川和富裕符文"
		7 "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚，生命，战争，河川，富裕和旅途符文"
		8 "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚，生命，战争，河川，富裕，旅途和崇山符文"
		9 "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚，生命，战争，河川，富裕，旅途，崇山和时光符文"
		10|# "符文匠可以使用太阳，束缚，生命，战争，河川，富裕，旅途，崇山，时光和威能符文"
	lang "French"
	10
		1 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil"
		2 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil et Lien"
		3 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien et Vie"
		4 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien, Vie et Guerre"
		5 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien, Vie, Guerre et Rivière"
		6 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien, Vie, Guerre, Rivière et Abondance"
		7 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien, Vie, Guerre, Rivière, Abondance et Voyage"
		8 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien, Vie, Guerre, Rivière, Abondance, Voyage et Montagne"
		9 "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien, Vie, Guerre, Rivière, Abondance, Voyage, Montagne et Temps"
		10|# "Peut faire de l'Artisanat runique en utilisant des Runes du Soleil, Lien, Vie, Guerre, Rivière, Abondance, Voyage, Montagne, Temps et Pouvoir"

description
	1 village_shipping_speed_+%
	1
		# "{}% increased Ship Speed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}%повышение скорости корабля"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Schiffsgeschwindigkeit"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Velocidad de los barcos aumentada un {}%"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มความเร็ว เรือ {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "운송 속도 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "船のスピードが{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "增加 {}% 船隻速度"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Velocidade da Exportação aumentada em {}%"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "船只速度提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Vitesse des Navires"

description
	1 village_smithing_speed_+%
	1
		# "{}% increased Smelting Speed"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "{}% повышение скорости переплавки"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "{}% erhöhte Verhüttungsgeschwindigkeit"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Velocidad de fundición aumentada un {}%"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "เพิ่มความเร็ว ถลุง {}%"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "제련 속도 {}% 증가"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "製錬スピードが{}%増加する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "增加 {}% 冶煉速度"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Velocidade da Fundição aumentada em {}%"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	1	
		# "冶炼速度提高 {}%"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "{}% d'Augmentation de la Vitesse de Fonte"

description
	1 village_tier16_maps_have_eldritch_or_maven_influence
	1
		# "Tier 16+ Maps have either Maven, Searing Exarch or Eater of Worlds Influence"
	lang "Portuguese"
	1
		# "Mapas Tier 16+ têm Influência da Maven, do Exarca Cauterizado ou do Devorador de Mundos"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	1
		# "階級 16 以上的地圖有釋界、灼烙總督或吞噬世界勢力"
	lang "Korean"
	1
		# "16등급 이상 지도에 메이븐 또는 작열의 총주교, 세계 포식자 영향력 적용"
	lang "German"
	1
		# "Karten des Levels 16+ haben entweder Einfluss der Seherin, des Brennenden Exarchen oder des Weltenfressers"
	lang "Russian"
	1
		# "Карты 16+ уровня будут находиться под влиянием Мейвен, Пламенного экзарха или Пожирателя миров"
	lang "Thai"
	1
		# "แผนที่ระดับ 16+ มีอิทธิพลของ เมเวน, อุปราชอาบเพลิง หรือ ผู้กลืนกินโลกา"
	lang "Japanese"
	1
		# "ティア16以上のマップはメイヴェン、シアリング・エグザークまたはイーター・オブ・ワールズのいずれかのインフルエンスを持つ"
	lang "Spanish"
	1
		# "Los mapas de grado 16+ tienen influencia de la Especialista, el Exarca abrasador o el Devorador de mundos"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"
	1
		# "16 阶及以上地图拥有贤主、焚界者或灭界者影响"
	lang "French"
	1
		# "Les Cartes de Palier 16+ ont une Influence soit de la Prodige, soit de l'Exarque ardent, soit du Mangeur de mondes"

description
	1 village_worker_generation_rank
	10
		1 "Recruits can specialise in Mining or Shipping"
		2 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting or Farming\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 2\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		3 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting or Farming\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 3\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		4 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting or Farming\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 4\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		5 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting, Farming or Disenchanting\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 5\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		6 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting, Farming or Disenchanting\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 6\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		7 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting, Farming, Disenchanting or Map Running\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 7\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		8 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting, Farming, Disenchanting or Map Running\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 8\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		9 "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting, Farming, Disenchanting or Map Running\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 9\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
		10|# "Recruits can specialise in Mining, Shipping, Smelting, Farming, Disenchanting or Map Running\nRecruits can have job specialty up to rank 10\nFaustus offers Black Market deals"
	lang "Portuguese"
	10
		1 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração ou Exportação"
		2 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Fundição ou Agricultura\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 2 na profissão"
		3 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação ou Agricultura\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 3 na profissão"
		4 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Fundição ou Agricultura\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 4 na profissão"
		5 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Agricultura ou Desencantamento\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 5 na profissão"
		6 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Agricultura ou Desencantamento\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 6 na profissão"
		7 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Fundição, Desencantamento ou Mapeamento\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 7 na profissão"
		8 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Agricultura, Desencantamento ou Mapeamento\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 8 na profissão"
		9 "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Agricultura, Desencantamento ou Mapeamento\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 9 na profissão"
		10|# "Recrutas podem se especializar em Mineração, Exportação, Fundição, Desencantamento ou Mapeamento\nRecrutas podem ter especialização rank 10 na profissão"
	lang "Thai"
	10
		1 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่หรือขนส่ง ได้"
		2 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่ หรือ เพาะปลูก ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 2\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		3 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่ หรือ เพาะปลูก ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 3\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		4 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่ หรือ เพาะปลูก ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 4\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		5 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่, เพาะปลูก หรือ สลายไอเทม ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 5\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		6 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่, เพาะปลูก หรือ สลายไอเทม ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 6\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		7 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่, เพาะปลูก, สลายไอเทม หรือ บุกแผนที่ ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 7\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		8 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่, เพาะปลูก, สลายไอเทม หรือ บุกแผนที่ ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 8\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		9 "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่, เพาะปลูก, สลายไอเทม หรือ บุกแผนที่ ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 9\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
		10|# "แรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญในการ ขุดแร่, ขนส่ง, ถลุงแร่, เพาะปลูก, สลายไอเทม หรือ บุกแผนที่ ได้\nแรงงานเกณฑ์ มีความชำนาญงาน สูงสุดระดับ 10\nฟาวทัส เสนอ สินค้าตลาดมืด"
	lang "German"
	10
		1 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau oder Schiffstransport"
		2 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung oder Landwirtschaft\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 2 haben"
		3 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung oder Landwirtschaft\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 3 haben"
		4 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung oder Landwirtschaft\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 4 haben"
		5 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung, Landwirtschaft oder Entzauberung\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 5 haben"
		6 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung, Landwirtschaft oder Entzauberung\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 6 haben"
		7 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung, Landwirtschaft, Entzauberung oder Kartenlauf\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 7 haben"
		8 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung, Landwirtschaft, Entzauberung oder Kartenlauf\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 8 haben"
		9 "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung, Landwirtschaft, Entzauberung oder Kartenlauf\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 9 haben"
		10|# "Rekruten können sich spezialisieren auf Bergbau, Schiffstransport, Verhüttung, Landwirtschaft, Entzauberung oder Kartenlauf\nRekruten können eine Berufsspezialisierung bis zu Rang 10 haben"
	lang "Russian"
	10
		1 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле или судоходстве"
		2 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке или земледелии\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 2 ранг своей специализации"
		3 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке или земледелии\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 3 ранг своей специализации"
		4 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке или земледелии\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 4 ранг своей специализации"
		5 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке, земледелии или распылении\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 5 ранг своей специализации"
		6 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке, земледелии или распылении\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 6 ранг своей специализации"
		7 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке, земледелии, распылении или исследовании карт\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 7 ранг своей специализации"
		8 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке, земледелии, распылении или исследовании карт\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 8 ранг своей специализации"
		9 "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке, земледелии, распылении или исследовании карт\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 9 ранг своей специализации"
		10|# "Новобранцы могут специализироваться в горном деле, судоходстве, переплавке, земледелии, распылении или исследовании карт\nНовобранцы могут иметь максимум 10 ранг своей специализации"
	lang "Spanish"
	10
		1 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería o comercio"
		2 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición o agricultura\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 2"
		3 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición o agricultura\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 3"
		4 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición o agricultura\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 4"
		5 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición, agricultura o desencantamiento\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 5"
		6 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición, agricultura o desencantamiento\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 6"
		7 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición, agricultura, desencantamiento o exploración de mapas\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 7"
		8 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición, agricultura, desencantamiento o exploración de mapas\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 8"
		9 "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición, agricultura, desencantamiento o exploración de mapas\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 9"
		10|# "Los reclutas se pueden especializar en minería, comercio, fundición, agricultura, desencantamiento o exploración de mapas\nLa especialización de trabajo de los reclutas puede ser hasta de rango 10"
	lang "Korean"
	10
		1 "신입이 채광 또는 운송에 특화 가능"
		2 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련 또는 경작에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 2단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		3 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련 또는 경작에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 3단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		4 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련 또는 경작에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 4단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		5 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련, 경작 또는 인챈트 해제에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 5단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		6 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련, 경작 또는 인챈트 해제에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 6단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		7 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련, 경작, 인챈트 해제, 지도 탐험에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 7단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		8 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련, 경작, 인챈트 해제, 지도 탐험에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 8단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		9 "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련, 경작, 인챈트 해제, 지도 탐험에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 9단계의 작업 특기 보유"
		10|# "신입이 채광, 운송, 제련, 경작, 인챈트 해제, 지도 탐험에 특화 가능\n신입이 최고 10단계의 작업 특기 보유"
	lang "Japanese"
	10
		1 "募集人員は採掘または輸送の専門能力を持てる"
		2 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬または農業の専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク2までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		3 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬または農業の専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク3までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		4 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬または農業の専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク4までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		5 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬、農業または解呪の専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク5までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		6 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬、農業または解呪の専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク6までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		7 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬、農業、解呪またはマップランニングの専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク7までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		8 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬、農業、解呪またはマップランニングの専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク8までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		9 "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬、農業、解呪またはマップランニングの専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク9までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
		10|# "募集人員は採掘、輸送、製錬、農業、解呪またはマップランニングの専門能力を持てる\n募集人員はランク10までの専門能力を持てる\nファースタスは闇市場取引を提供する"
	lang "Traditional Chinese"
	10
		1 "新人可專精開採或運送"
		2 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉或耕種\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 2\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		3 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉或耕種\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 3\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		4 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉或耕種\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 4\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		5 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉、耕種或破幻\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 5\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		6 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉、耕種或破幻\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 6\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		7 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉、耕種、破幻或地圖探索\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 7\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		8 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉、耕種、破幻或地圖探索\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 8\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		9 "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉、耕種、破幻或地圖探索\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 9\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
		10|# "新人可專精開採、運送、冶煉、耕種、破幻或地圖探索\n新人的工作專精最高階級為 10\n弗斯特提供黑市交易"
	lang "Simplified Chinese"	
	10	
		1 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘或航海"
		2 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼或耕作\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 2\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		3 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼或耕作\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 3\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		4 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼或耕作\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 4\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		5 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼、耕作或分解\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 5\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		6 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼、耕作或分解\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 6\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		7 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼、耕作、分解或异界冒险\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 7\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		8 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼、耕作、分解或异界冒险\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 8\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		9 "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼、耕作、分解或异界冒险\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 9\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
		10|# "新招募人员可以专精于采掘，航海，冶炼、耕作、分解或异界冒险\n新招募人员的岗位专长最多为等级 10\n浮士德可提供黑市交易"
	lang "French"
	10
		1 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage ou la Navigation"
		2 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte ou l'Agriculture\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 2\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		3 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte ou l'Agriculture\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 3\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		4 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte ou l'Agriculture\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 4\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		5 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte, l'Agriculture ou le Désenchantement\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 5\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		6 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte, l'Agriculture ou le Désenchantement\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 6\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		7 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte, l'Agriculture, le Désenchantement ou l'Exploration des Cartes\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 7\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		8 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte, l'Agriculture, le Désenchantement ou l'Exploration des Cartes\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 8\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		9 "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte, l'Agriculture, le Désenchantement ou l'Exploration des Cartes\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 9\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"
		10|# "Les Recrues peuvent avoir pour spécialité le Minage, la Navigation, la Fonte, l'Agriculture, le Désenchantement ou l'Exploration des Cartes\nLes Recrues peuvent avoir une spécialité allant jusqu'au rang 10\nFaustus propose des offres du Marché noir"

